The experiments we've run so far
prove that the D-Mails are being sent to the past.
But I couldn't change the outcome of my match with Faris!
That's a problem with you, not with the D-Mail.
There are problems with the system,
including the issue with Lukako,
but if we work on it, we can turn it into a real time machine...
Time machine?
You were listening to us?
Faris just brought your order!
Do you want any maple syrup or milk?
I refuse!
Then you can have my everything!
There it is!
Secret Move: Stir While Gazing Into Their Eyes!
I'm so jealous I could explode, Okarin.
Kyouma, what do you mean by a time machine?
Do you think you can seduce me
into giving up classified information?
I won't ask Kyouma then.
Daru-nyan!
You think Daru would betray me?
We built a machine that sends texts to the past,
and by "we," I mean mostly me!
That was entirely too fast!
Messages to the past?
Even the billions of heartbeats in the world
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
are nothing to you but insignificant
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Whether we’re trapped in the past or lamenting over the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
predetermination does not allow even the slightest mistake
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The infinite dreams and futures before us
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are but vain privileges allowed to us
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finitude is what both clock hands show
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
toward a cruel destiny and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
So now I cross worldlines every second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
because I want to protect that smile of yours
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And so, a time loop without sadness will once again
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
engulf me, the lone observer
Chaos Theory
Homeostasis
Stupid Daru...
spreading our secrets to outsiders...
Why?
Why must you take it that way?
I just wanted to...
No, that's not what I meant!
I...
Wh-Wh-What?
I'm not crying!
It's not like I was crying, okay?
You were clearly crying...
Your eyes are still red.
No way!
Something's in my eye...
What is this, an old soap opera?
Anyway, I'm not crying,
so no questions.
Got it?
I didn't say anything.
Shut up!
Cristin—
Shut up! Don't talk to me!
I'll just say this...
You're an important ally.
Any time you want to talk, I'll listen.
Okabe...
Just as planned, she fell for it!
Now I can use her for all the grunt work!
Hey.
Good work out there!
Faris!
Are you heading to Kyouma's?
Yeah, he wanted me to bring lunch.
Hey, have you seen the time machine, Mayushii?
Time...
Oh, the PhoneWave?
PhoneWave?
There's this big sparky thing, and it's kind of scary...
Wow!
It's like a time machine out of the movies.
Yeah...
But Mayushii doesn't really want him doing that stuff.
Why?
It feels like Okarin is leaving me.
We will now begin our Round—
Okarin! Okarin!
What?
Isn't this strange?
Mayushii says she isn't cosplaying.
It isn't cosplay.
It's her school uniform.
I had school today.
It's a super-realistic portrayal of a school uniform.
That's sexual harassment, and she doesn't have to put up with it.
Here's yours, Okarin!
Thanks.
No, wait. I said we're having a Round Table!
You're the one who wanted me to bring lunch.
Don't mind him.
Obviously, it isn't anything important.
You can say that after you hear the discussion topic...
Physical time travel!
Mayuri, is there still barley tea in the fridge?
One second.
Realistic.
It's me!
The Organization has initiated an operation to tear apart the lab.
Hououin Kyouma's words, my words,
fail to reach them!
Do they ever?
Then why are you ignoring my awesome topic?
Because it's impossible.
We can send messages to the past.
It must be possible...
It's not.
We can send 36 bytes plus some extra.
Three messages, each with six characters.
No more.
If you want to experiment, why not be the guinea pig?
That's if you don't mind ending up as a gel-Okarin.
Gel-Okarin, huh?
That'd really hurt.
SERN's experiments demonstrate the difficulties
inherent to physical time travel.
Even using the LHC, the largest particle accelerator in the world,
they've had no success.
We can't possibly do it with this equipment.
Then how do the messages get to the past?
I don't know.
That's the problem.
As I said before,
SERN's trying to use the lifter-black hole combination
to achieve time travel.
The PhoneWave probably works on the same principle.
But the microwave doesn't have anything
to function as a lifter.
So where is it?
I don't know.
We're limited in the times we can send D-Mail too.
Currently, we can't be sure that this machine
really sends messages to the past.
Before we continue,
we should deal with more relevant issues first.
Boring!
99.9% of science is boring.
If you call yourself a scientist...
I'm not a scientist!
I'm a mad scientist!
This guy is hopeless. Better do something quick.
Miss Makise...
Don't tell me you're...
Shut up!
Not another word!
Because that's impossible!
Get back on topic already.
Continuing on to the reports,
how's the translation of
SERN's server documents going, Christina?
Or should I say, @channeler?
I told you that's not true!
Then you sure know your memes.
I do not!
There's nothing to report.
I see.
Continue your investigations...
@channeler!
Stop calling me that!
Daru's up next. How's the hacking coming?
No change.
Until I analyze the mysterious program
on the other server, there'll probably be no change.
How's the IBN 5100 analysis going?
It'd be great if I could do it.
What do you mean?
Huh?
You haven't started the analysis?
How would I do that?
Where's the IBN 5100?
How would I know?
That can't be...
Okarin, what's wrong?
Christina...
did I, by any chance, fail to find the IBN 5100?
You don't even know where it is.
I see.
So if I choose to believe what you say, you found the IBN 5100.
Yes.
I carried it back here with you.
But you're the only one with any memory of that.
The D-Mails probably changed the past.
Changed the past...
But we've only sent minor stuff.
It's the butterfly effect.
Sending one message into the past
causes the worldline to split,
from a world where we didn't buy a LOTO SIX ticket
to one where we did.
Little by little, this changes what was meant to happen.
One change causes another,
and they pile on top of one another.
It's one of the long-recognized risks of altering the past.
Then where is the IBN 5100?
Let me ask this instead:
where was it?
Yes, when I asked my dad, he said it used to be here, but...
It's gone now.
I see.
Well?
There was an IBN 5100 at Yanabayashi Shrine,
but it's gone now.
No one knows when it was taken or by whom.
A dead end, huh?
But it's strange to donate a PC to a shrine.
I wonder who would do that.
Faris?
What's up?
Here's the list of ten questions I wrote
to ask the maids at the next event.
Let me see...
"If you could go back and redo one thing from your past, what would it be?"
What would you do, Faris?
Let me think...
Faris... doesn't look back on her past! Let's go.
It's the task of the cat-eared maid,
who brings everyone happiness, to forge ahead!
Oh, my phone!
Hi, this is Faris.
Kyouma.
A PC?
An IBN 5100.
Did your family give it to Yanabayashi Shrine?
I don't really remember...
but you're right. My daddy did have a lot of old PCs.
Kyouma...
is this related to the time machine
you were talking about?
Look, look!
It's an Upa!
A metal Upa!
Do you still want a metal Upa?
Still?
How long are you going to stand there staring at it? Let's go.
Wait!
Daru!
Here I am!
What did you buy now?
I found a limited-edition that sold out before I could buy it!
As you might say,
"This encounter was the choice of Steins Gate!"
Don't use it for stuff like this!
Anyway, why are you two following me?
You could've stayed back at the lab with the assistant.
Once I heard you were going to Faris's place,
I had to come along!
I wanted to go and play too!
Why did Faris tell me to come to her house?
It's Kirari!
Mayuri, wait...
Geez...
The IBN 5100.
Shining Finger!
Wait! Hey!
Shining...
Moeka!
Kiryu Moeka!
Why?
FB said it was there!
Okabe...
Back there, you mentioned the IBN 5100...
Do you know where it is?
You don't know either?
I don't.
Okarin!
Moeka?
Yeah.
Okabe...
Moeka's so pretty and stylish.
I'm sure she'd make a great cosplayer.
Mayuri, you know Shining Finger?
I do!
How?
How do you know her?
You brought her to the lab!
After Moeka sent her D-Mail,
she disappeared from everyone's memory.
And then, after Luka sent his D-Mail,
they knew her again.
Little by little, the world changes
each time a D-Mail is sent to the past then?
Is this really the place?
I'm sure of it.
Seems it's on the top floor.
The mistress will be here soon.
Just one moment.
Butler cafés aren't my thing.
A real butler!
I've never seen one before.
Look!
Everyone looks like ants!
I love it!
Okarin...
Figures he'd say that.
Sorry for the wait.
Faris!
Now it's Faris wearing her normal clothes!
What luck!
Faris NyanNyan!
It seems I must question your true identity!
Faris is...
...Faris, nyan!
Stop fooling around!
If you refuse to explain, then I'm leaving!
Oh, fine.
Faris's family owns all the land around here!
Then Akiba is...
That's right.
What about Akiba now?
It's Faris's real name.
Akiha Rumiho!
I didn't hear that!
Faris's real name is Faris!
What a sad attempt to escape reality.
By the way, Faris was the one
who asked to bring the culture of moe to Akiba.
No way!
And she works as an angel at MayQueen
to further spread the culture of moe!
How splendid!
And my eyes are also splendid for recognizing her before anyone else!
But, but... keep it a secret, okay?
I want you to treat me
with Faris-love, just like you always have!
I will! Totally!
Thank you, nyan-nyan!
No nyan-nyans!
Anyway, what about the IBN 5100?
Oh, that?
But before that, I have a simple request...
You want to arrange a trade?
It's nothing difficult.
I only want you to let me use the D-Mail, just once.
Of course!
Use it as much as you want!
Wait! The D-Mail is absolutely off-limits to outsiders...
Then why not make Faris a lab mem too?
Wait! Wait!
Sending more messages to the past would be—
You're the one who sent the LOTO SIX number back to try and make money,
yet you won't send one for Faris?
Just this once!
No, that's not it...
But if I stop now,
there's no guarantee that the IBN 5100 will return.
If this is any indication...
Very well.
But as Mayuri said,
you'll have to become a lab mem.
You are now Lab Mem 007, Akiha Ru—
I-I-I can't hear you!
It's done.
You're sure you want to send it back ten years, right?
I'm sure!
What does it say?
Well... it's a secret!
Tell me.
As leader of the lab, it's my job to know.
No. A maiden's private life is off-limits to guys.
I think it's wrong to look at someone's emails.
I agree! Totally!
Fine.
Then put your hand on the send button and wait.
Hallo?
It's me!
What's the situation...
She hung up on me, dammit!
Yeah, I bet she did.
That Christina!
Doesn't she know she's my assistant?
Hallo?
It's Hououin Kyouma. Don't just hang up on me without a word.
Hououin? Oh, Okabe.
I thought it was a prank call.
I'm sure you saw my number on the display.
Even so, those first words
were creepy enough to make me hang up.
In other words, you are terrified of the mighty Hououin Kyouma—
She hung up on me! She hung up on me again!
Okarin, aren't you ready yet?
Wait!
Curse you, cold-blooded pervert girl genius...
Hallo?
Listen, the Zomb—
Hello, my name is Okabe Rintaro.
What is it?
I would be eternally grateful
if you'd set the PhoneWave (name subject to change)
to the values I proferred in my earlier message.
You should have just said that from the start.
Also, that isn't what "proffer" means.
You're embarrassing yourself.
And stop calling it the PhoneWave (name subject to change) already.
Shut up, Celeb Sev!
I'm trying to be polite, and you're...
Do they not like each other?
I think it's the opposite.
Agreed.
Will you send?
Maybe...
Maybe I don't need to do this.
Faris!
The electricity's started.
Send it.
Um...
Who are you?
Daddy!
"Daddy"?
Were you talking to Kyouma?
Yeah.
I'll be on my way.
Enjoy yourselves.
Faris's dad has this
kind of refined air about him, doesn't he?
Indeed! You can tell he's Faris's dad.
Um...
Do you know anything about an IBN 5100?
I haven't heard that name in ages.
I'm looking for one.
Unfortunately, I parted with mine a long time ago.
Did you give it to Yanabayashi Shrine?
Shrine?
No, I didn't.
Goodbye, then.
Before Faris sent her D-Mail,
I heard that the IBN 5100 disappeared after it had been given to Yanabayashi Shrine.
But now, the shrine never got it.
Each time we send a message, things change.
Something may be changing,
even without me being aware of it.
It's possible that we've already done something that can't be undone.
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
With my field of view restricted
Okarin! Okarin!
Mayushii is going to Nakano to buy a Lovely Sword comic.
Lovely Sword?
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
I cannot escape the merciless control of the twelve
Kouga Yui?
Nakano's far away.
Yeah.
I wish there was a Toranoana comic shop here.
ansoku no asu wo negatta
While wishing for a tomorrow of repose
What are you talking about?
Toranoana's right over there.
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
I headed for the sacred event horizon in my hand
What are you talking about, Okarin?
Why would there be one in Akiba?
Pledges are imprisoned, and false evidences are showing their outline
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
This world of life blindly lets the time pass by
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
Spread your wings
habatake butterfly
butterfly of miracles
kiseki no butterfly
I dedicate it to you
anata he sasagu
Oh butterfly of tears
namida no butterfly
butterfly of radiance
mabushii butterfly
everything will now be rewritten
subete ga ima kakikaerareru